Guide to the Miles Galvin Manuscript on a Comparative Analysis of Labor Movements 1984-1988
Galvin, Miles Manuscript on a Comparative Analysis of Labor Movements
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Miles Galvin Manuscript on a Comparative Analysis of Labor Movements, 1984- 1988
6372
Galvin, Miles
0.5 linear ft.
Papers.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
CONTAINER LIST
- Tasks and Outlines, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Chapter 1: Why Comparisons Are Important, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Chapter 2: Why Comparisons Are Important, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Chapter 3 (Old): The Contrasting Ideologies of Labor Movements, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Chapter 4: Labor Movements With the Ideology of Revolutionary Class Confrontation, Focus on France, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Chapter 5: Focus on Germany, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Chapter 6: Labor Movements With the Ideology of Nationalist Class Collaboration, Focus on Mexico, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Chapter 7: The Problem of Job Security and the Swedish Labor Movement's Efforts to do Something About It, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Chapter 8: Income Insecurity, Declining Productivity, and What's Happening in Japan, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Chapter 9: Working Conditions and the Struggle for Worker Self-Management, Focus on Israel, Spain, Yugoslavia, Norway (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Chapter 10: The Struggle of Black Workers in Racist South Africa, A Cutting Edge in the Fight for Worker Liberation in the First World, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Chapter 11: Solidarity's Struggle in Communist Poland, A Second-World Cutting Edge in the Fight for Worker Liberation, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Chapter 14: American Labor's Foreign Policy, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)